I couldn't say goodbye
Ienai ienai sayonara nante
even though I love you so much
Konna ni daisuki na no ni
You said we should break up
Mou wakareyou to
Kimi no koe ga kikoeta shunkan
and when I heard that
my world turned white in an instant
Mou masshiro ni natte
Karadajuu ni hashitta hibana
and sparks danced in my vision
Is forgetting you what I need
Kimi no koto wo wasureru koto ga
Mae ni susundeku koto na no?
to move on?
I could cry now, I don't understand
Wakaranai yo nakete kuru yo
Let's live in the moment, only in the moment
Seiippai meiippai ima wo ikiyou
We lived like that until now, too, I guess
Sou yatte ikite kita kedo
I couldn't say goodbye
Ienai ienai sayonara nante
Konna ni daisuki na no ni
even though I love you so much
何が悲しくて　お前と　初売りを
攻めなくちゃならないんだ？
So how the hell did I end up at a New Year's sale with you?
We have to collect supplies.
（左門）身の回りの品を
そろえる必要があるだろう。
And there are other requested items.
ほかに
頼まれたものもあるしな。
Didn't know you wore such flashy underwear.
随分　派手なの　はくんだな。
（左門）お前の着替えだが。
These would be for you.
羽村とかいう絶園の魔法使い→
Isn't someone meeting with this Hanemura
who's supposed to be the mage of Exodus?
今頃　どっかで
顔合わせしてんだろ？
俺が不用意に近づかないよう→
Didn't you bring me out here to keep me away from the guy?
連れ出しとくのが
目的なんじゃねぇのか？
ピッピッ（車のアンサーバック音）
（左門）それもある。
That's part of it, but...
だが　物事には段取りがあろう。→
There is an order to things.
It should be obvious
お前と会わせる前に→
that we must confirm his identity before we let you see him.
こちらで　先に人物確認するのが
当然ではないか？
そいつ　本物なのか？
Is he the real thing?
姫様の見立てでは　間違いなく。
According to the princess, there's no doubt about it.
（葉風・心の声）≪羽村めぐむ…≫
Hanemura Megumu.
His power is, without a doubt, the power of a mage of Exodus.
≪あの力は　間違いなく
本物の絶園の魔法使いだが→
But that makes him a suspect in Fuwa Aika's murder.
それは同時に　不破愛花殺害の
容疑者ということでもある≫
≪果たして真広は　どう動くか…≫
I wonder what Mahiro's next move will be...
吉…　ん？
Yoshi—
なんか
流されてる気がするけど…。→
I really don't know
Subject: I'll be waiting for you
優しい人だといいなぁ。
how I feel about this...
（山本）
ということで　よろしく　羽村君。
And so, it's nice to meet you, Hanemura-kun!
（羽村）あっ　はい。
R-Right.
My name is Evangeline Yamamoto.
（山本）
私は　エヴァンジェリン山本。
フロイライン山本と
呼んでくれればいいわ。
You can call me Fräulein Yamamoto.
（羽村）か…　変わったお名前ですね。
That's a unique name.
（山本）あっ
こちらは　魔法使いの夏村君。→
Oh, this is Natsumura, a mage.
Just call him Natsu.
親しみやすく
ナッツと呼んであげてね。
（夏村）呼ばんでください。
ふふっ。　さて　羽村君→
Please do not call me that.
Well then, Hanemura...
まずは
いろいろ聞かせてくれるかな？
Why don't you start by telling us more about yourself?
S-Sure.
はっ　はい。
≪ああ…　優しい人でよかった≫
Thank goodness she's so nice.
So now you're the chauffeur?
いつの間にか運転手か？
（哲馬）運転だけではない。→
Driving is not my only role.
左門殿に何かあれば
ボディーガードにもなる。
Should anything happen to Mr. Samon, I would act as his bodyguard.
ふっ　誰が今更。
Who would bother now?
矢印野郎だからって
逆走するんじゃねぇぞ。
Don't go driving into opposite traffic or anything just because you have an arrow on your face.
（左門）
目覚めて間もないというのに→
It hasn't been long since you awoke,
but you haven't stopped talking.
口数が減らんな。
それより　お前→
More importantly, I'm surprised you haven't given up.
よく諦めないでいられるな。
何がだ？
On what?
You had a plan you'd worked on for many years,
お前は　長年かけた計画が
冗談みたいな展開で→
and it got foiled rather badly, as if it was some kind of joke.
あっという間に
砕かれるなんて奇跡を→
くらわされたばかりだぞ。
（左門）ふっ。　不破真広→
Fuwa Mahiro.
もし　お前が
滅んだ世界を目の前に→
Suppose the world was destroyed,
and a god appeared before you,
そこに　神様が現れたとする。→
「お前が
どうやっても　この結果を→
would you prefer that it say that you could have done nothing to change the outcome?
変えられなかったのだ」
と言われるのと→
Or that, had you not given up,
you might have affected the result?
「お前が諦めねば　この結果は
変えられたのだ」と言われるのと→
どちらがいい？
嫌な神様だな。
What an annoying god.
（左門）神とは　そういうものだ。→
That is the nature of a god.
諦めたあとで　実は
勝ち目があったと言われるのなら→
Rather than being told after giving up that I'd had a chance,
I would prefer being told that I couldn't have done anything,
諦めなかったあとで
勝ち目がなかったと言われる方が→
after refusing to give up.
私は　マシと思うわけだ。→
How about you?
お前ならどうだ？
Your sister could have been killed
妹を殺したのは→
by the logic of the Tree of Genesis.
はじまりの樹の理かも
しれんのだぞ。
Would you then abandon your revenge?
ならば　途中で復讐を投げ出すか？
Do I really look that weak-willed to you?
お前には
俺が　そんなまともに見えるのか？
ふっ。　お互い　往生際が悪いな→
Apparently neither of us knows when to give up, Fuwa Mahiro.
不破真広。
Mahiro is just fine.
「真広」でいい。
名字　一緒に呼ぶな。
Stop using my full name.
こんな感じですけど…。
It's something like this.
He did that with such ease.
≪かくも　たやすく…≫
（夏村）魔法を使うのに　手続きや
供物を必要としないのか？
Do you not need any contracts or offerings to use magic?
Not really.
（羽村）はい。　こんなふうに出すぞ
ってイメージするだけで…。
I just think about doing it, and it happens.
Do you feel physically or emotionally exhausted?
（夏村）体力や精神力の消耗は？
（羽村）さあ？
I'm not sure.
（夏村）≪手続きなしで
消耗の実感もなく…≫
He doesn't require offerings, and displays no sign of fatigue.
That's disconcerting.
≪なんと剣呑な≫
（山本）
≪葉風さんの見立てどおり→
Just as Ms. Hakaze said,
he doesn't look like he knows how to use his power.
いかにも使えなさそうね≫
Then how accurately can you attack an enemy?
（夏村）では　どれくらいの正確さで
相手を攻撃できる？
Um...
（羽村）えっと…。
Let's see.
≪例えば
この樹だけを消し去るイメージで…≫
What if I imagine making this one tree disappear?
（山本）何やってんのよ！
What the hell were you doing?!
（羽村）たっ　試しに　ちょっと…。
（山本）ちょっとじゃないでしょ！
It was was just a little test...
That wasn't "little"!
以後
こっちの許可なく魔法を使うな！
From now on, don't use magic without our permission!
Yes, ma'am...
はい　約束します！　うぅ…。
まったく！
I swear!
Damn it.
≪あんまり
優しい人じゃなかった≫
She isn't all that nice after all.
あっ　あの…。
んん…。
Um...
And now, I would like to begin
（山本）ええ～
では　これより　羽村めぐむ君の→
Hanemura Megumu's interrogation regarding his murder charge.
殺人容疑に関する
取り調べを行いたいと思いま～す。
Eh?!
どっ　どういうことなんですか!?
（山本）絶園の魔法使いには→
What do you mean?
Well, the mage of Exodus has been charged with murder.
ある殺人容疑がかかってるの。
（羽村）でも→
But...
I...
僕…。
（左門）そう身構えるな。
Don't be so nervous.
I don't intend to go on and on with questions.
くどくど聞く気はねぇ。
一つだけ答えろ。
For now, just tell me this.
On November 23rd, one year ago,
今から　約１年前の１１月２３日→
from 10 PM until midnight,
午後１０時から午前０時の間→
where were you?
お前　どこにいた？
えっ？　えっ？
Huh? What?
その日そのとき
俺の妹が殺された。
My younger sister was killed on that day, at that time.
I found her body the next morning.
翌朝　俺が死体を発見した。
We still don't know who the killer was.
いまだに　犯人は分からねぇ。
それは気の毒に…。
I'm very sorry to hear that.
I don't want your pity or sympathy.
同情も感傷もいらねぇ。
And besides, considering the current state of the world,
それに　今の世の中の状況じゃ→
it's hardly the worst thing to happen.
どちらかというと　マシな話だろ？
ただ俺は　愛花を殺した犯人が→
I just can't forgive the fact
that Aika's killer may still be alive.
生きて存在しやがるのが
許せねぇだけだ。
It doesn't make any sense at all.
それは
不合理で　辻褄が合わねぇからだ。
I will do whatever it takes
それが正せるんなら→
俺は　何とでも引き換えにする。
to right that wrong.
Um...
（羽村）あの…。
ああ？
Who's Aika?
（羽村）愛花って誰？
My younger sister, obviously!
俺の妹だよ！
文脈から読み取れるだろ！
You couldn't put that together?!
Put together?
文脈って言われても…。
ったく！
Jeez.
Anyway, after using magic to find the killer,
とにかく
魔法を使って　犯人を捜した結果→
絶園の魔法使いが
最有力容疑者として挙がった。
the mage of Exodus is the prime suspect.
答えろ　１１月２３日の深夜→
Answer me.
What were you doing on the night of the 23rd?
どこで何をしていたのか。
そんな…。→
But...
１年以上も前のことなんて…。
That was over a year ago.
（羽村）ちょっ…　ちょっと待って。
おととしの１１月って→
Hold on!
November of the year before last should be...
確か…。
ピッ　ピッ
あっ　そうだ。　やっぱり。→
That's right, it was.
On that date and time, I was with Yu.
その日そのとき
ゆっちゃんと一緒にいたんだ。
ゆっちゃん？
（羽村）うん。→
Yu?
Yeah.
She's my girlfriend. We've been dating since my junior year,
高校２年のときから
つきあってる彼女で→
and her skin is white as snow, so I call her Yu!
肌が雪みたいに白いから
ゆっちゃんって呼んでるんだ。→
She's pretty harsh in general, but she can be really cute, too.
基本　厳しいけど
かわいいとこもあって…。
I don't care.
知らねぇよ。
じゃあ　その女に確認すれば
アリバイは証明できるのか？
So if we spoke to her, we'd know if you did have an alibi or not?
Yeah, but...
（羽村）できるけど→
ゆっちゃんに
会わせるわけにはいかない。
I won't let you see Yu.
Why not?
なんでだ？
（羽村）この件は
おかしなことばっかりだ。→
This whole situation is too weird.
どんな危険があるか分からない。
I don't know what kind of danger we'll be in.
I don't want to drag Yu into this!
ちょっとでも
ゆっちゃんを巻き込みたくない。
へえ～。
ふっ。
（羽村）それに→
Well, that and
she recently dumped me, so things are pretty awkward.
最近　振られたばっかりで
いろいろ気まずいんだ。
メールも電話も
拒否されちゃってるし→
She won't reply to my calls or texts,
and I heard that she might have moved away...
引っ越したっていう　うわさも…。
Then you couldn't meet with her to begin with!
それ　お前自身すら会えねぇだろ！
（羽村）あはは…。
もういい。
（羽村）それじゃあ→
Whatever.
Does that mean my name's been cleared?
僕の疑いは晴れたの？
いいや。
No.
It just means I'll have to ask your body directly.
あとは　直接　お前の体に聞く。
Huh?
What?!
（羽村）
痛っ！　何すんだよ!?　うっ…。
Ow!
What was that for?
Go ahead and use magic or whatever you want.
魔法でもなんでも使っていい。
Try to do what I just did, and drop me on the floor.
同じように　俺を床に倒してみろ。
（羽村）なんでも使っていいって…。
I can use whatever I want?
ぼっ　僕は
絶園の魔法使いなんだよ!?
But I'm the mage of Exodus!
Yeah, you are.
そうだな　本気で殺しに来られたら
ひとたまりもないが→
While it'd be bad if you actually killed me...
それができるようなヤツなら→
If you manage to do it, then you could have killed Aika, as well.
同じように　愛花も殺せたはずだ。
そっ　そんな…。
B-But...
Even if I died here,
仮に　俺がここで死んだとしても→
吉野と葉風は
俺の敵を討ってくれるだろうなぁ。
I'm pretty sure that Yoshino and Hakaze would avenge me.
≪相変わらず
駆け引きのうまいヤツだ≫
He hasn't lost his edge in driving a hard bargain.
≪まともな者なら
ああ言われると慎重になる≫
Any normal person would become cautious after hearing that.
Even if Hanemura were hiding his true nature as a ruthless man,
≪また　羽村が意図を持って
冷酷な心を隠していたとしても→
この状況で　不用意に　姫様を
敵に回す道は選ばんだろう≫
he wouldn't chance making the princess his enemy while so ill-prepared.
ほら　立てよ。
（羽村）くっ…。
Come on, stand up.
ふっ
お前　そんな　だらしないから→
Your girlfriend probably left you because you're so pathetic.
彼女に振られたんじゃないのか？
いや　そもそも
彼女だったかどうかも怪しいなぁ。
In fact, I'm starting to doubt she even was your girlfriend.
Indeed.
（左門）うむ。　実在はするが→
Even if she exists,
it's also possible that those feelings were completely one-sided.
一方的に彼女と思い込んでいる
可能性もあるな。
ああ～。　はははっ
お前　ストーカーか　なんかか？
Maybe you're a stalker or something?
Eh, stalker dude?
おい　ストーカー野郎。
僕は…。
I...
僕は～！
ふっ。
I...
I'm not a stalker!
ストーカーなんかじゃない！
あっ！
ドカッ！
It's far too obvious that you have no intention of hitting me.
当てる気ないの　バレバレだぞ。
If you're going to come at me, do it like you're about to break off my limbs.
やるなら　俺の手足
ぶった切るつもりでやれ。
≪どうしよう
なんか勝てる気がしないよ…≫
What am I going to do?
I don't think I can win.
His strength is undeniable,
（左門）≪力は本物だが
心が　ああも弱いとは…≫
but with such a weak heart...
≪やはり　滝川吉野の方が
絶園の魔法使いとしては…≫
It seems more plausible that Takigawa Yoshino is the mage of Exodus.
≪ヤツらも
何か企んでいるようであり→
It's possible that he's plotting something, though,
so we shouldn't lower our guard.
一層
油断ならんことになりそうだな≫
Presumably, the tree here was destroyed yesterday afternoon,
（官僚）さすがに　これ以上は
抑えられませんでした。
Unfortunately, this is about as far as we could contain the media.
Tree Suddenly Disappears
It disappeared overnight!?
Where did the tree go?
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（アナウンサー）近隣住民の話では
特に異音なども…。
but according to area residents,
Well, it's not that surprising.
（山本）まっ　しかたないわね。→
they neither heard nor knew how it disappeared.
After all, he did erase a whole tree.
あれだけ
派手にやっちゃったんだから。
Internet rumors suggest
（官僚）
ネット上では　絶園の魔法使いの→
it may have been the mage of Exodus's work.
仕業だという　うわさも。
（早河）ほう。
For once, the rumors are actually true.
うわさじゃなくて
事実なんだけどね。
（官僚）えっ？
（早河）気にするな。　ほかには？
Don't worry about it. Anything else?
（官僚）これを。
This.
An overseas investigative team has gone to Mt. Fuji.
（官僚）海外からの調査団が
富士へ入山しました。→
They're there as backup.
あくまで
支援活動の一環ではありますが。
These guys aren't idiots.
（早河）連中も
それほど　まぬけじゃない。→
They're bound to find out the Kusaribe clan's secret.
すぐに　鎖部の秘密にも
たどりつくだろう。
（山本）まずいじゃない　それ！
That's not good!
No, we've been on the defensive up until now.
いや
これまで　防戦一方だったが→
２つとも　こちらから攻める
いい武器になる。
This may be a good opportunity to go on the offensive.
随分　楽しそうね。
You seem to be enjoying this.
（官僚）
早く中央に戻ってくださいよ。→
Please return to central soon.
If there is any further development, I will contact you.
また動きがあれば連絡します。
（山本）例の件も早急？
And the other urgent matter?
Before that, we must persuade Kusaribe Samon.
（早河）その前に
鎖部左門を説得する必要がある。
And...
それと…。
あのお姫様ね。
The princess, as well.
（一同）きゃあ～～！
行こ　行こ　早く。
あっち　あっち　あっち！
They're acting like couples.
（葉風）いちゃいちゃしてるな。
（滝川吉野）
いちゃいちゃしてますね。
They are indeed.
And in this cold, too.
（葉風）寒いのに　よくやるな。
よくやりますね。
（葉風）はぁ…。
Indeed.
何か　うそのようだな。
It's almost like it never happened.
Around a billion people disappear overnight,
１０億単位の人間が
一夜で消失し→
and the world has been greatly changed,
世界は　異形に
変容させられたというのに→
but couples everywhere are celebrating the new year,
以前と変わらず
恋人同士は　新年を祝い→
without a care.
こうして歩いている。→
It just seems wrong that they have no sense of danger.
こんな危機感のない風景が
あっていいものか…。→
我々は　まともな感覚さえ→
Maybe the Tree also rewrote our very emotions.
大樹に書き換えられて
しまったのではないか…。
I don't think that's the case.
それは違います。
ん？
はじまりの樹が
こうして現れる前から→
Even before the Tree of Genesis appeared,
there was war, starvation,
世界では
戦争や飢え　犯罪や災害→
crime, natural disasters,
貧困や病で　毎日
何万という死者が出ていました。
poverty, and illness that claimed tens of thousands throughout the world.
Yet no one really had a sense of danger.
なのに　危機感なんて
誰も持ってやしませんでしたよ。
何億　死のうと
もともと　世界は　こんなです。
It doesn't matter if billions have died.
This is how the world has always been.
ふふっ。　いっそ　今は→
In a way, it's like we paid in advance with those many lives.
死者の数を先払いしたみたいに→
But now, there is no war,
世界中から争いがなくなり
歴史上→
so this may be the most appropriate time for people to feel at ease.
最も　この光景がふさわしい時代に
なっているのかもしれませんよ。
少し不思議だな。
はい？
What unusual sang-froid you have.
What?
I'm saying that your point of view contains a bit of "SF."
お前の物の見方は
ＳＦ的だということだ。
ＳＦの略は
「少し不思議」じゃありませんよ？
SF is the abbreviation for sci-fi, not sang-froid.
あっ　それも　ありだったかな？
Okay, so maybe it was that too...
Not to mention, I don't know what you're thinking at times.
しかも　時々
どこを見ているか分からん。
ん？
視野が広いのか狭いのか→
I can't tell if you're narrow or broad-minded.
And I can't tell if you're kind or just cold.
優しいのか冷たいのかも
はっきりせんぞ。
はあ…　すみません。
謝るようなことではない。
Oh, sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
≪結局→
In the end,
this is apparently how things should be.
今のままが
いいということなのか…≫
（潤一郎）やあ　１週間ぶり。
Hey!
Haven't seen you in a week.
あ…　相変わらず
唐突だな　潤兄さん。
Abrupt as always, aren't you?
More importantly, Yoshino,
（潤一郎）それより　吉野君。
はっ？
これで　あったかいコーヒー
買ってきてくれるかな→
can you get us some coffee with this?
三人分。
（葉風）潤兄さん→
For all three of us?
Jun, don't treat Yoshino like a servant.
吉野に
使い走りのまねをさせるなど…。
It's fine, I'll be right back.
いいですよ。　じゃあ。
なんの用だ？　潤兄さん。
What do you want, Jun?
わざわざ
吉野に席を外させてまで。
Making Yoshino leave like that...
Did you realize, Hakaze,
葉風ちゃんさ→
吉野君に恋してるよね？
that you're in love with Yoshino?
はあ～？
（一同）きゃあ～～！
What?!
ドカッ！
（羽村）うっ！　ううっ！
You're finally getting better.
だいぶ　マシになってきたな。
これだけ器用に切れるんなら→
If you can cut this precisely, try cutting through my bone.
派手に骨まで　ぶった切れよ。
だから→
I already told you I'm afraid of blood!
血を見るのが怖いんだよ！
しょうがねぇな。
You're hopeless.
（山本）調子はどう？
（夏村）この数日間の特訓で→
How's it going?
Over these last few days of training,
his magic has improved, if only slightly.
僅かではありますが
魔法の精度も向上しています。→
However, his lack of emotional fitness for this is a concern.
しかし　あまりに　精神が
弱すぎるのが気になりますが。
≪確かにね≫
It's true that mentally,
≪精神面で言えば
吉野君の方が…≫
Yoshino would be...
By the way,
そういや
お前　はじまりの樹を倒そうと→
I heard you were headed to Mt. Fuji, to defeat the Tree of Genesis?
富士に向かってたんだって？
（羽村）うっ　うん…。
Y-Yes.
It's amazing you would even consider that.
そんなんで　よく
そんな大それたことを考えたな。
（羽村）それは→
Well...
I thought that maybe if I saved the world, Yu would approve of me.
世界を救ったら　ゆっちゃんに→
見直してもらえるんじゃないか
って…。
You're doing this for the chick who dumped you?
振られた女のためにって
不純な動機だな。
Talk about unreasonable.
そんなこと　シスコンの君に
言われたくないよ！
I don't want to hear that from someone with a sister complex like you!
Huh?!
≪よくぞ言ってやった≫
Well said.
The one thing everyone wanted to say.
（山本）≪誰もが
１回は言ってやりたかった≫
The forbidden words.
（哲馬）≪禁断の言葉を…≫
Who has a sister complex?
誰がシスコンだ　誰が！
For starters, Aika and I aren't related by blood.
だいたい
愛花とは　血はつながってねぇ。
So she may legally be my sister,
戸籍の上では妹だが
実際は　妹でもなんでもねぇんだ。
but she actually isn't my sister at all.
だから　シスコンじゃねぇ。
それ→
So I don't have a sister complex!
That's not even a sister complex...
シスコンどころか…。
どころか？
What?
ただの恋なんじゃ…。
It sounds like you're in love with her.
Love?!
（葉風）恋～!?
What are you saying, Jun?
何を言ってるんだ　潤兄さん。
違うかい？
Am I wrong?
Of course you're wrong!
違うに決まっている。
I would never consider a younger weakling like that as a potential love interest.
あんな年下のうらなりなど
恋愛対象になるものか。
First of all, Yoshino has a girlfriend.
第一　吉野には
彼女がいるのだぞ？
It's already strange that someone like him has a girlfriend.
まったく…　ああいう男に
彼女がいるのも希有な話だ。
That, in itself, is pretty much a miracle.
それこそ奇跡であろう。
うんうん　それで？
Yes, yes, and...
（葉風）だが　あやつは
大した男ではあるがな。→
But he is quite impressive in his own way.
富士での
剛腕にして　緻密な駆け引きでは→
At Mt. Fuji, he effortlessly devised a brilliant strategy
死ぬような目に遭いながら
気にしたふうもない。→
even in the face of death.
His courage can only be qualified as extraordinary.
胆力は非凡というほかなく
かと思えば→
And yet, he's very considerate and has a sensitive side.
実に　こまやかで
気が利くところもあり…→
まだ若いゆえ　至らぬ点も多いが→
He's still rather young and has things he needs to work on,
but on the other hand, if he didn't, he wouldn't be so lovable.
それくらいなければ愛嬌がない。
体つきは　なよっとしてそうで→
He might look like a weakling,
意外に　肉づきや胸板は
しっかりしていて…。
but his muscles and his chest are surprisingly firm.
あっ
いや　触れたことはないのだが。
Well, not that I've ever touched them...
というか　触ってはダメだろう！
Or rather, I shouldn't touch it!
If I were to touch something, his earlobes seem like they
触れるなら
耳たぶとか　ちょうどよく→
might just be soft enough.
柔らかそうで　ひと晩中でも→
I think I could touch them all night long.
触っていられる気がするな。→
And I'd like to comb through his hair.
髪の毛も　こう　くしとかで
とかしてやりたいと。→
Oh, right!
あっ　うん　そうだな。
温泉地に行く予定もあるので→
And we have plans to visit a hot spring, so that's an opportunity right there.
そのときにでも…。
You want to touch and fondle his earlobes?
触りたいとか耳たぶとか→
See? You're totally in love.
それ　完全に恋してるよね。
えっ？
Huh?
してるのか？
So I am in love.
そうでもない相手の耳たぶを→
Otherwise, wanting to fondle someone's earlobes
ひと晩中でも触っていられる方が
怖いかな。
all night long would be a little disturbing.
（葉風）はっ！　そういえば…。
Now that you mention it...
When I saw him earlier,
（葉風）あやつが携帯で→
staring at a picture on his phone, possibly of his girlfriend,
じっと　彼女の写真らしきものを
見つめているのに気付いて→
I instantly felt frustrated and yet lonely...
なぜか
猛烈に腹が立つやら寂しいやら…。
そうか　それでだったのか！
I see! That was the reason!
恋！
Love!
Love?
恋だぁ？　バカ言え。
Don't be stupid.
妹に恋する兄がいるわけないだろ。
There's no way a brother would fall in love with his younger sister.
いっ　いや
さっき　妹じゃないって…。
But you just said she wasn't your sis—
うわっ！
休憩だ。
We're taking a break.
ありがとう。
忘れるなよ。
Thanks.
Don't forget.
I still think that you may have killed Aika.
まだ俺は　お前が
愛花を殺したかもしれないと→
疑ってるんだぞ。
≪ガチャ　バタン（ドアの音）
（山本）意外と　いいコンビかもね。
They make a surprisingly good duo.
By the way, has that other matter finally begun?
（哲馬）ところで
例の計画　いよいよ実行か？
Hayakawa is on his way right now to persuade your boss.
（山本）今まさに　早河が
あなたたちの主を説得中よ。→
堅実第一のあの人が
素直に同意するかどうか…。
Considering that he values stability above all else, will he go along with the plan?
（夏村）左門殿は　堅実といっても→
Although Mr. Samon values stability,
he is also willing to bet for the sake of that stability.
堅実に大勝負される方でも
あるのですけれど。
The design has been finalized and is now being manufactured.
すでにデザインは終え
製作に入っている。
（早河）我々は　あまりにも
はじまりの樹と絶園の樹を→
We know too little
about the Tree of Genesis and the Tree of Exodus.
知らなさすぎる。→
What kind of gods are they?
二つの樹は　どういう神なのか。→
Exactly how much control do they have over the world's logic?
理を　どれほど操れるのか。→
How long has the Tree of Genesis existed?
はじまりの樹は
いつから　そこにあったのか。
この計画は　そこまで白紙にして
考えるきっかけになる。
This plan will let us reexamine everything from square one.
どうだ？
確かに　鎖部一族にとって→
Well?
It's true that to the Kusaribe, magic and the Tree
魔法は　樹は　あまりに
身近でありすぎるゆえ→
are both so intertwined,
前提から
誤って捉えていたおそれはある。
that we may have been held captive by false assumptions.
計画に手を貸そう。
I will assist with your plan.
However, I will not permit any unsupervised decisions during its execution.
ただし　この先　実行において→
勝手な判断は認めんぞ。
無論だ。　あとは…。
Of course. All that's left...
姫様が
なんとおっしゃるかだが…。
...is what the princess will say, but...
...that may be difficult.
（早河）てこずりそうだな。
ああ。　内容からすると→
Indeed.
Considering the subject, persuading her will take a while.
説得には　時間がかかるだろうな。
Do whatever you want.
好きにしろ！　何かあっても
私が　はじまりの樹に干渉すれば→
Even if something were to happen, I can take care of the Tree!
すぐ収まろう！
[TEL]（左門）しっ　しかし→
B-B-But...
W-Without even knowing the nature of this plan...
けっ　計画の詳細も知らないまま…。
[TEL]（葉風）くどい！
You talk too much!
You sure that was okay?
（潤一郎）いいのかい？
（葉風）大した話ではない。→
It wasn't important.
More importantly, Jun...
それより　潤兄さん
私は　これからどうすればいい？
What am I supposed to do now?
まさか
吉野に恋してしまうなど→
How could I have fallen in love with Yoshino?
こんなこと予定にないぞ！
That was not my plan at all!
You don't usually plan for these things.
予定して恋するのも
どうかと思うけどね。
それはともかく→
But either way, it probably isn't a good idea to love Yoshino.
吉野君を好きになるのは
まずいよ。
I know that.
分かっている。　今は　色恋に
うつつを抜かしている場合では…。
Now isn't the time to consider a love affair.
That's not what I mean.
そういう意味じゃなくて
吉野君には　彼女がいるだろ？
Yoshino has a girlfriend.
あっ…　うむ。
It's unproductive to fall in love with someone who has a girlfriend.
彼女がいる相手を
好きになるのは不毛だな。
That isn't what I meant, either.
そうじゃなくてさ→
葉風ちゃんが
吉野君との関係を強く望むなら…。
If you were to desire a relationship with Yoshino strongly enough,
the Tree of Genesis would kill that girlfriend.
その彼女
はじまりの樹に殺されるよ。
いけ　いけ～！
Come shake hands with me under the Tree of Genesis!
（山本）
はじまりの樹の下で　僕と握手！
（羽村）あっ　あの…→
U-Um, this...
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
これ　まさか…→
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
Don't tell me this is...
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
An Announcement from the Mage of Exodus
On 1/21, after 9 PM,
I will destroy
the Tree of Genesis
visible in the following locations.
Those who are invited,
please bear witness.
Rain or Shine
僕のことですか!?　えっ？→
...about me?!
ん？
（山本）絶園の魔法使い→
The mage of Exodus
will finally make his major debut!
メジャーデビューだ！
えっ？→
Huh?!
Episode 15
You Seem to Be
Plotting Something
kimi no utatta hanauta ga
The song you hummed
boku no hanauta to kasanatta
and the song I hummed were the same
yoku aru koto kamoshirenai kedo
Maybe this is not so rare,
tokubetsu datte omoitainda
but I'd like to believe it's special
tokidoki fuan ni mo naru kara
Sometimes everyone feels anxious
tsui mata sagashite shimaundayo
and we wind up seeking it again
me ni mienai ito no youna
Like an invisible string,
futari wo tsuyoku tsunagi au mono
it is what connects us two
tatoe hoka no dare ga waratte mo
Even if others laugh about that,
boku wa tsuyoku shinjiteru kara
I believe it exists,
ima mo zutto zutto negatte iruyo
and so I keep on wishing even now
futari de iru mirai wo
for a future where we are together
mae wo muite aruite yuku yo
I will look ahead and walk
hitori kiri janai kara
because I am not alone
itsu no hi ka kimi to hora unmei datta ne tte
I hope we can one day laugh and say "Hey, it was destiny"
issho ni waraeru to ii na
Wouldn't that be nice?
（哲馬）幽霊など
ただの気の迷いにすぎん。
Ghosts are mere delusions.
幽霊か…。
でも　なんか　おかしいですね。
Ghosts, huh?
But it's funny, isn't it?
（葉風）いや
ここは　怖がってみせた方が→
But if I appeared scared here, would I look cuter?
かわいげがあるというものか？
（老婆）うぶな娘が色気づいたら
手に負えんがの。
Once an innocent woman realizes her sensuality,
she becomes impossible to handle.
（山本）まだ序の口よ。
だんだんと派手にしていくから。
This is just the beginning!
We'll make it even flashier.
（羽村）ご飯は!?　お風呂は!?
What about food? What about bathing?
（老婆たち）ひゃははははっ！
Episode 15
The Wandering Apparition